Guide to the Religious Education Association Records - Addendum A
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Meetings, 1972-2003; Series IV
  - Convention, Toronto, "The Open Society: Shaping Religion and Values", 1973 (Box 13, Folder 156)
  - Eastern Regional Conference, Atlantic City, "Models of Teaching For Religious Faith", 1974 (Box 13, Folder 157)
  - 75th Anniversary Conference, Chicago, "This We Can Believe: A Pluralistic Vision", 1978 (Box 13, Folder 158)
  - Convention, Toronto, "Tomorrow's Child Today", 1979 (Box 13, Folder 159)
  - Conference, New York University, "Religious Education and Public Policy", 1981 (Box 13, Folder 160)
  - Conference, Anaheim, California, "Pursuing Justice and Peace: Challenge to Religious Educators", 1983 (Box 13, Folder 161-162)
  - Fall Conference, Washington, DC, "Spirituality and Religious Education", 1986 (Box 13, Folder 163-164)
  - Conference, Toronto, "How Shall We Sing the Lord's Song in a Strange Land? Faithful Educating in a Pluralistic Culture", 1987 (Box 13, Folder 165-166)
  - Conference, Boulder, Colorado, "The Living Earth: Home of God and All God's People", 1990 (Box 14, Folder 167-168)
  - Conference, Indianapolis, "Adult Learners: Making Critical Connections", 1992 (Box 14, Folder 169)
  - Conference, Indianapolis, planning, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 170-171)
  - Conference, Indianapolis, Adult Education Bibliography, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 172)
  - Conference, Indianapolis, Resource on Persons with Disabilities, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 173)
  - Conference, Indianapolis, Notebook, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 174)
  - Conference, Chicago, "Nurturing Learning Communities; Building Learning Linkages", 1994 (Box 15, Folder 175-177)
  - Conference, Chicago, Bibliography, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Conference, New Orleans, "Congregation as Educator", 1996 (Box 15, Folder 179-180)
  - Conference, New Orleans, Exhibits, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 181)
  - Conference, Orlando, Florida, "Spiritual Meaning and Religious Commitment", 1998 (Box 15, Folder 182-183)
  - Conference, Orlando; Paul Limbert, correspondence, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 184-185)
  - Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, "Learning to See God in the Peoples of God", 2000 (Box 16, Folder 186-187)
  - 100th Anniversary Conference, Chicago, "Embracing the Past, En- visioning the Future: Religious Education in an Age of Transition", 2003 (Box 16, Folder 188-191)
  - 100th Anniversary Conference, Proceedings, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 192)
  - Lilly Endowment Grant, "Educational Conferences on Religious Differences" (Box 17, Folder 193-194)
  - Tri-Lateral Conference, Houston, Texas, "The Use of the Sacred Texts in Forming the Faith of the Community", 1991 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Tri-Lateral Conference, Houston, Papers, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 196)
  - Tri-Lateral Conference, Claremont and Los Angeles, CA, "E Pluribus Unum: Religious Pluralism and the Common Good", 1992 (Box 17, Folder 197-198)
  - Tri-Lateral Conference, Stony Point, NY, "Multifaith Dialogue in a Multicultural Society", 1993 (Box 17, Folder 199-200)
  - Tri-Lateral Conference, Oklahoma City, "Archetypes and Prototypes: Role Models in Islam, Judaism and Christianity", 1993 (Box 18, Folder 201)
  - Tri-Lateral Conference, Oklahoma City, Papers, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 202)
  - Tri-Lateral Conference, Windsor, Ontario, "Religious Wisdom on Contemporary Issues: Muslim, Christian and Jewish Perspectives", 1994 (Box 18, Folder 203)
  - Tri-Lateral Conference, Pittsburgh, PA, "Making a Difference: An Interfaith Conference on Moral Education", 1994 (Box 18, Folder 204)
  - Tri-Lateral Conference, Villanova, PA, "Particularity and Pluralism: Educating for Religious Identity and the Common Good", 1994 (Box 18, Folder 205)
  - Tri-Lateral Conference, Stony Point, NY, "Teach a Woman, Teach a People", 1994 (Box 18, Folder 206)
  - Tri-Lateral Conference, Stony Point, NY, Resources, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 207)
  - Tri-Lateral Conference, Stony Point, Papers, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 208)
- Regional Work, 1988-1989, n.d.; Series V
  - Chapters, Metropolitan and Regional (Box 19, Folder 209)
  - Chapters, Listings, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 210)
  - Regional Chapter. Houston, Texas, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 211)
  - Chapter Symposium, Houston, Texas, "Religious Education: Survival in a Secular Society", 1989 (Box 19, Folder 212)
  - Symposium, Spertus College, Chicago, "Religion at Risk", 1988 (Box 19, Folder 213)
- Publications, 1971-2003, n.d.; Series VI
  - 75th Anniversary of the Religious Education Association, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 214)
  - John Westerhoff, Who Are We? The Quest for a Religious Education. Birmingham, AL: Religious Education Press, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 214)
  - Stephen A. Schmidt, A History of the Religious Education Association. Birmingham, AL: Religious Education Press, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 214)
  - Boardman Kathan, Ed. "Pioneers of Religious Education in the 20th Century," Religious Education, Special Edition, 1978 Sep-Oct (Box 19, Folder 214)
  - 100th Anniversary of the Religious Education Association, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 215)
  - Journal, Religious Education, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 216)
  - John L. Elias, Religious Education in Adulthood. New Haven, CT: Religious Education Association, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 217)
  - Journal Issue, "Religious Traditions in Conversation", n.d. (Box 20, Folder 218)
  - Advertising in the journal, Religious Education, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 219)
  - Reprint permissions, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 220-221)
  - Membership Directory, 1991, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 222)
  - Cassette tapes, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 223)
  - Chronicle Guidance Publications, "Religious Education Directors" (Box 20, Folder 224)
  - R.E.A. Website, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 225)
  - Tri-Lateral Conferences, plans for publication, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 226)
  - Press releases, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 227)
  - Newsletter, R.E.A. Directors, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 228)
  - Newsletter, The Religious Educator, 1971-1973 (Box 21, Folder 229)
  - Newsletter, The Religious Educator, REACH, 1974-1976 (Box 21, Folder 230)
  - Newsletter, REACH, 1977-1980 (Box 21, Folder 231)
  - Newsletter, REACH, 1981-1986 (Box 21, Folder 232-233)
  - Newsletter, REACH, 1987-2003 (Box 22, Folder 234-238)
- Research, 1979-1989; Series VI
  - Faith Development in the Adult Life Cycle Project, 1979-1987 (Box 23, Folder 239)
  - FD/ALC Symposium, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 240)
  - FD/ALC Symposium, Papers, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 241)
  - FD/ALC Symposium, Hypotheses, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 242)
  - FD/ALC Symposium, Book; Kenneth Stokes, Ed. Faith Development in the Adult Life Cycle. New York, NY: W. H. Sadlier Co., 1982 (Box 23, Folder 243)
  - FD/ALC Pretest, Gallup Organization, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 244)
  - FD/ALC, Steering Committee, 1982-1985 (Box 23, Folder 245-246)
  - FD/ALC, Regional Conferences, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 247)
  - FD/ALC, Module 1; "Faith Development and Your Ministry," Princeton Religion Research Center, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 248)
  - FD/ALC, Module 2, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 249)
  - FD/ALC, Module 2 Revised, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 250)
  - FD/ALC, Steering Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 251)
  - FD/ALC, Final Report, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 252)
  - FD/ALC, Seminar-at-Sea, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 253)
  - Book: Kenneth Stokes, Faith is a Verb: Dynamics of Adult Faith Development. Mystic, CT: Twenty-Third Publications, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 254)
  - Adult Faith Resources, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 255)
  - Annual Review of Research, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 256)
  - Bibliographies, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 257)
- Financial and Promotional Records, 1981-2001; Series VIII
  - Annual Financial Reports, 1983-1993 (Box 25, Folder 258-259)
  - Financial Reports, 1995-1999 (Box 25, Folder 260)
  - IRS Return, 990, 990-T, 1983-1990 (Box 25, Folder 261-266)
  - Staff payroll, New Haven, CT, 1981-1997 (Box 25, Folder 267)
  - Financial reports, 1982-2001 (Box 26, Folder 268-270)
  - R.E.A. Treasurer, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 271)
  - Bank accounts, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 272)
  - Wornom Retirement Housing Reserve Fund (Box 26, Folder 273)
  - Promotional records, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 274)
  - Promotional brochures, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 275)
  - Pew Trust, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 276)
  - Lilly Endowment (Box 26, Folder 277)
  - Theological Education by Extension, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 278)
  - Endowment Fund (Box 26, Folder 279)
  - Hagedorn Fund (Box 26, Folder 280)
  - University Microfilms, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 281)
  - Religious Education Press, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 282)
  - Martin Quigley, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 283)
- Memberships, 2001; Series IX
  - Membership lists (by country, zip code, alphabetical by last name), 2001 (Box 27, Folder 284)
- Photographs, 1970-2000, n.d.; Series X
  - A-B-C (Rabbi Hanan Alexander, Joyce Bailey, Fr. Howard Basler, Jerry Benjamin, Peter Berger, Jerome Berryman, Myron Bloy, Rabbi Eugene Borowitz, Mary Boys, Milo Brekke, John Bremer, Rabbi Balfour Brickner, Fr. Donald Campion, Ruth Shonle Cavan, Joanne Chafe, Rabbi Burton Cohen, Harvey Cox, Ronald Cram, Clarisse Croteau-Chonko, Iris Cully) (Box 27, Folder 285)
  - D-E-F (Sr. Dorothy Davis, Fr. Roger Desmarais, Fr. Robert Drinan, Gloria Durka, Alexander Dushkin, Craig Dykstra, Findley Edge, David Elkind, Donald Emler, Emil Fackenheim, Sophia Lyon Fahs, Roy Fairchild, Trenton Ferro, J. Blaine Fister, Fr. Edward Flannery, Charles Foster, Fr. Matthew Fox, Dorothy Jean Furnish ) (Box 27, Folder 286)
  - G-H-I (Sr. Ann Ida Gannon, Dolores Gerken, Rabbi Arthur Gilbert, Ronald Goldman, Roberta Goodman, Eli Grad, Fr. Andrew Greeley, Rabbi Irving Greenberg, Rabbi Simon Greenberg, Thomas Groome, Howard Ham, Maria Harris, Warren Hartman, Daniel Heischman, Carter Heyward, Fr. Johannes Hofinger) (Box 27, Folder 287)
  - J-K-L (Jesse Jackson, Belva Brown Jordan, Sr. Teresita Kambeitz, Rabbi Mordecai Kaplan, Boardman Kathan, Will Kennedy, Malcolm Knowles, Lawrence Kohlberg, Fr. C. Albert Koob, Paul Lederach, James Michael Lee, Ernest Ligon, Robert Lynn), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 288)
  - M-N-O (Fr. Berard Marthaler, Martin Marty, Paul Maves, Fr. Alfred McBride, Fr. Richard McBrien, Fr. John McCall, Neil McCluskey, with Richard U. Smith, Bishop William McManus, Charles Melchert, Robert Michaelsen, Randolph C. Miller, with Herman Wornom, et al, Randolph C. Miller, with Glenn Garbutt, Allen Moore, Gabriel Moran, Ernest Nedder, C. Ellis Nelson, Roberta Nelson, Richard Neuhaus, David Ng and Greer Anne Ng, Michael Novak, Robert O'Gorman, Karen O'Neal, Harry Orlinsky) (Box 27, Folder 289)
  - P-Q-R-S (Marion Pardy, Rabbi W. Gunther Plaut, Ira Progoff, Robert Raikes, Larry Randen, Lawrence Richards, Herbert Richardson, Donald Russo, Barbara Ryan, Barbara Ryan with Barbara MacCameron, Br. Leo Ryan, Dorothy Savage, Dorothy Savage with Boardman Kathan and David Gray, Philip Scharper, Alvin Schiff, Peter Schillaci, Stephen Schmidt, Jack Seymour, Rabbi Morris Sherer, Rabbi Byron Sherwin, Charles Silverman, Sidney Simon, Nelle Slater, Catherine Smith, Richard U. Smith, Raymond Smolover, Eliot Spack, Rabbi Jack Spiro, David Stanley, Robert Steffer, Kenneth Stokes, Olivia Pearl Stokes, Leon Sullivan, Rabbi Daniel Syme) (Box 27, Folder 290)
  - T-U-V-W-X-Y-Z (Mary Lee Talbot with Barbara Withers, Rabbi Marc Tanenbaum, Fr. William Tobin, Margaret Tyree, Paul Vieth, Anton Vrame, Sr. Annette Walters, Sr. Ann Patrick Ware, Cynthia Wedel, Luther Weigle, John Westerhoff with Greer Ann Ng, Elisa Wheeler, Elie Wiesel, David Wilkerson, Howard Williams, Anne Wimberly with Martin Marty, Herman Wornom, Elisabeth Watson, et al), n.d. (Box 27, Folder 291)
  - R.E.A. Convention, Chicago, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 292)
  - R.E.A. Convention, Toronto, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 293)
  - R.E.A. Convention, Philadelphia, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 294)
  - R.E.A. Convention, St. Louis, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 295)
  - 75th Anniversary Conference, Chicago, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 296)
  - R.E.A. Convention, Toronto, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 297)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970-1980s (Box 27, Folder 298)
  - Installation of Boardman Kathan as General Secretary, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 299)
  - R.E.A. Staff, Officers, Board members, 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 300)
  - 65th and 70th Anniversary of the Journal, Religious Education, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 301)
  - Writers Conference and Yale-Hartford-Berkeley Consultation, 1973, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 302)
  - Testimonial Dinner for Boardman Kathan, NYC, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 303)
  - R.E.A. Board of Directors, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 304)
  - R.E.A. Staff and Editorial Staff, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 305)
  - R.E.A. Board of Directors (Spring meeting), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 306)
  - R.E.A. Board of Directors, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 307)
  - Symposium, Spertus College, Chicago, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 308)
  - Conference, Boulder, Colorado, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 309)
  - R.E.A. Board of Directors, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 310)
  - R.E.A. Board of Directors and Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 311)
  - Conference, Indianapolis, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 312)
  - Tri-Lateral Conference, Claremont and Los Angeles, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 313)
  - Tri-Lateral Conference, Oklahoma City, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 314)
  - Parliament of the World's Religions, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 315)
  - Tri-Lateral Conference, Stony Point, NY, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 316)
  - R.E.A. Conference, Chicago, Illinois, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 317)
  - R.E.A. Board of Directors, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 318)
  - New R.E.A. Office, Columbia Theological Seminary, Decatur, GA, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 319)
  - R.E.A. Conference, Orlando, Florida, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 320)
  - R.E.A. Annual Meeting at APRRE Meeting, Toronto, Ontario, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 321)
  - R.E.A. Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 322)
  - R.E.A. Exhibits, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 323)